const quiz = {
    name: 'Friends',
    questions:[
    {
        question:"How many babies did Phoebe carry for her brother?",
        choices:[1, 3, 0, 2],
        answerIndex: 1
    },
    {
        question:"Where did Phoebe and Mike get married?",
        choices:["On the street", "In a church", "In a park", "They never got married"],
        answerIndex: 0
    },
    {
        question:"The 'Geller Cup' is a prize in which sport?",
        choices:["Hockey", "Basketball", "Football", "Rugby"],
        answerIndex: 2 
    },
    {
        question:"Whose catchphrase is 'Oh my GOD'?",
        choices:["Phoebe","Ross","Janice","Chandler"],
        answerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question:"How many friends have worked in the coffee shop?",
        choices:[1, 5, 3, 2],
        answerIndex: 3
    },
    {
        question:"What type of animal is 'Hugsy'?",
        choices:["Lion","Penguin","Rabbit","Bear"],
        answerIndex: 1
    },
    {
        question:"Who was the holiday Armadillo?",
        choices:["Joey","Mike","Chandler","Ross"],
        answerIndex: 3
    },
    {
        question:"Who plays 'Will', an old friend of Monica and Ross from High School?",
        choices:["Bruce Willis","Paul Rudd","Brad Pitt","Michael Rapaport"],
        answerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question:"What does Monica's dad give her to compensate for ruining her childhood possessions?",
        choices:["Porsche","Money","House","Nothing"],
        answerIndex: 0
    },
    {
        question:"Where is Chandler forced to work after falling asleep in a meeting?",
        choices:["Yemen","Atlantic City","Las Vegas","Tulsa"],
        answerIndex: 3
    }]
};